[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "How does it feel to be back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Are you still proud of CNN?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Do you still watch CNN?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "I watch it, you bet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Do you like what you see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "I like most of what I see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "If you had the competition that's around now in cable when you first started, in other words, if there had been a FOX News with right-wing star anchors, MSNBC had Rachel Maddow and the others, would you do anything differently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I'd have to really give it a lot of thought and a lot of study, which I have not done, because nobody has asked me to do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rachel Maddow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "But do you think that CNN should remain the impartial observer of news?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"]}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "What do you think of your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I think it's terrible that politics have gotten so money oriented with this Supreme Court ruling that the corporations can give unlimited amounts, that the moneyed interests are taking over the country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "How is he doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I like him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Where do you think he's not been strong enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, I would have liked to see him be -- his positions are good on the environment, but he put health care ahead of the energy bill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Is that really what America should have done, rather than going in with men on the ground, big, large phalanxes of troops, actually say we're going to tackle the terrorists through intelligence, through Special Forces and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "I think -- I think war should be avoided at all costs.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "What would you do about Iran if you were the American president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, first of all, I believe in total nuclear disarmament.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "What do you feel, Ted, when you see that like clip again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "I feel good.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "JJR", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "What did you really want to achieve with CNN?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I wanted to better inform the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Do you feel that you succeeded?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "How many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Over 100.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Was that the story, the event that made you realize just how big CNN could become?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "What do you think the difference that decision, that capability made to the way the war was covered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I -- you know, just all we did was televise what we saw.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "But did it bring a greater truth, do you think, to war coverage, the fact that you were there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Your third story that you singled out, 9/11, the CNN coverage of that, what did that do to America, that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "CD", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Well, it shook us up.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Ted, Jane Fonda, was she the great love of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane Fonda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Have you ever quite got over her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "You want me to rank them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Which upset you the most?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "They all broke my heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AOL"]}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBR", "VBN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ":", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Are you a better man for having experienced loss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I'm a more experienced man, because those -- you know, the AOL merger and the subsequent -- basically destruction of my wealth, they hurt at the time, but I just toughed it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What does that feel like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "It felt -- it felt bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "How does that feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "It really hurt, because we were making our budget and I was loyal to the management of the company.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Well, most men watching this will be going, come on, Ted, how did you get away with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RBS", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "With great difficulty.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Are they good friends with each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "URNER: Some of them are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Did you try and win her back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "A little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Twice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "But there's a difference between being in love and loving?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Sort of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "What should America be doing now to revive itself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "I think what we need is for humanity to be great.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "What do you think of the concept of moral capitalism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I'm working so hard on the environment and nuclear weapons and the survival issues that the financial -- the financial issues and a lot of other areas, you can't be an expert on everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 409, "question": "But does it help America and its national interests if very successful American companies that create their ideas here, then shift out much of the production jobs to other countries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "VB", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Has money made you happy, happier than you would have been without money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Having some, you've got to have enough to eat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "So five is the optimum number?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "No, I could have had three.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 462, "question": "You've given up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "On -- my doctors said I was allergic to potatoes, so I couldn't --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "URNER: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Any alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Tobacco?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Hard drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Coca-Cola"]}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What are you allowed to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "I can't even drink a Coca-Cola, you know, no soft drinks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "What are you existing on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I'm -- water.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Who's going to win, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", ":", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Are you more Republican or Democrat these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I'd like to say that right now, in the last few years, the Democrats have been closer -- have been more pro-environment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "What was your overview of his tenure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I -- a lot of the things that he did I didn't agree with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "RP", "RB", ",", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "All the things that you've experienced, what's been the greatest moment of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "The greatest single thing is to see my children all turn out well, all five of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "And have they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "URNER: They have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120528pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Is that your proudest achievement?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "My proudest personal achievement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]